Andrew Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Andrew Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson papers
1833-1980 (bulk 1900-1980)
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Dasburg, Andrew
8.8 linear feet
The papers of painter Andrew Dasburg and his wife and sculptor Grace Mott Johnson date from 1833 to 1980 (bulk 1900 to 1980), and measure 8.8 linear feet. The collection documents each artist's career and personal lives, including their brief marriage and their friendships with many notable artists in the New Mexico and New York art colonies during the early twentieth century. The papers of Dasburg (6 linear feet) and Johnson (2.8 linear feet) include biographical materials; extensive correspondence with family, friends, and fellow artists, such as John F. Carlson, Mabel Dodge Luhan, Marsden Hartley, Henry Lee McFee, and Ward Lockwood; writings by Dasburg, Johnson, and others; scattered legal, financial, and business records; clippings; exhibition materials; numerous photographs of Johnson and Dasburg, friends, family, and artwork; and original artwork, including two sketchbooks by Johnson.
Provenance
The Andrew Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson papers were donated by their son, Alfred Dasburg, in 1980.
Separated Material
In 1989, Syracuse University loaned materials related to Andrew Dasburg for microfilming on reels 2803 and 4276-4278. Loaned material is available for viewing on microfilm, but is not described in the container listing of this finding aid.
Related Material
Also found in the Archives of American Art are two oral history interviews with Andrew Dasburg, July 2, 1964 and March 6, 1974. Additional related collections at other repositories include the Andrew and Marina Wister Dasburg Papers at the New Mexico State Archives, the Andrew Dasburg Papers at Syracuse University Library, and the Grace Mott Johnson Papers at the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Alternative Forms Available
The bulk of the Andrew Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson papers were digitized in 2007 and are available on the Archives of American Art's website.
Restrictions on Access
The collection has been digitized and is available online via AAA's website.
Biographical Note
Andrew Michael Dasburg (1887-1979) was born in Paris, France, to German parents. After his father died and when he was five, Dasburg and his mother moved to New York City. In 1902 Dasburg started attending classes at the Art Students' League and studied with Kenyon Cox and Frank Du Mond. He also took night classes with Robert Henri. In 1907 he received a scholarship to the Art Students' League summer school in Woodstock, New York and spent three summers studying there in Birge Harrison's painting class. While in school he became friends with many young artists, including Morgan Russell and his future wife, Grace Mott Johnson.
Grace Mott Johnson (1882-1967) was born in New York City. She began drawing when she was four years old, and when the family moved to a farm in 1900 she enjoyed sketching horses and other farm animals. At the age of 22 she left home to study at the Art Students' League with sculptors Gutzon Borglum and James Earle Fraser, and also attended Birge Harrison's painting class in Woodstock. Throughout her career she would sculpt animals from memory, and would often attend circuses and farms for inspiration.
In 1909 Johnson and Dasburg went to Paris and joined the modernist circle of artists living there, including Morgan Russell, Jo Davidson, and Arthur Lee. During a trip to London that same year they were married. Johnson returned to the United States early the next year, but Dasburg stayed in Paris where he met Henri Matisse, Gertrude and Leo Stein, and became influenced by the paintings of Cezanne and Cubism. He returned to Woodstock, New York in August and he and Johnson became active members of the artist community. In 1911 their son Alfred was born. Both Dasburg and Johnson showed several works at the legendary Armory Show in 1913, and Dasburg also showed at the MacDowell Club in New York City, where he met the journalist and activist John Reed who later introduced him to Mabel Dodge (Luhan), a wealthy art patron and lifelong friend. In 1914 Dasburg met Alfred Stieglitz and became part of his avant-garde circle. Using what he had seen in Paris, Dasburg became one of the earliest American cubist artists, and also experimented with abstraction in his paintings.
Dasburg and Johnson lived apart for most of their marriage. By 1917 they had separated and Dasburg began teaching painting in Woodstock and in New York City. In 1918 he was invited to Taos, New Mexico by Mabel Dodge, and returning in 1919, Johnson joined him there for a period of time. Also in 1919, Dasburg was one of the founding members of the Woodstock Artists Association with John F. Carlson, Frank Swift Chase, Carl Eric Lindin, and Henry Lee McFee. In 1922 Dasburg and Johnson divorced, and also at that time he began living most of the year in Santa Fe with Ida Rauh, spending the rest of the year in Woodstock and New York City. Dasburg became an active member of the Santa Fe and the Taos art colonies, befriending many artists and writers living in these communities, and remaining close friends with Mabel Dodge Luhan. Here he moved away from abstraction, and used the southwestern landscape as the inspiration for his paintings.
In 1928 he married Nancy Lane. When that marriage ended in 1932, he moved permanently to Taos, and with his third wife, Marina Wister, built a home and studio there. Dasburg periodically taught art privately and at the University of New Mexico. In 1937 he was diagnosed with Addison's disease, which left him unable to paint again until 1946. In 1945 he and his wife Marina separated. Dasburg was recognized for his career as an artist in a circulating retrospective organized by the American Federation of Arts in 1959. He also had retrospectives in Taos in 1966 and 1978. His artwork influence several generations of artists, especially in the southwest, and he continued creating art until his death in 1979 at the age of 92.
Grace Mott Johnson lived in the Johnson family home in Yonkers, New York during the 1920s and later moved to Pleasantville, New York. In 1924 she went to Egypt to study ancient Egyptian sculpture. During the 1930s she became a civil rights activist. She produced very little art during the last twenty years of her life.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of painter Andrew Dasburg and sculptor Grace Mott Johnson date from 1833 to 1980, with the bulk of the materials dating from 1900 to 1980, and measure 8.8 linear feet. The collection is divided into the papers of Andrew Dasburg (6 linear feet) and the papers of Grace Mott Johnson (2.8 linear feet), and documents each artist's career and personal lives, including their brief marriage, and friendships with many notable artists in New Mexico and New York art colonies during the early twentieth century. Found are scattered biographical, legal, and financial materials. Extensive correspondence (particularly in Dasburg's papers) is with family, friends, and fellow artists, such as John F. Carlson, Florence Ballin Cramer, Mabel Dodge Luhan, Marsden Hartley, Henry Lee McFee, Vera Spier Kuhn, and Ward Lockwood. Dasburg's papers also include letters to Johnson and his two later wives.
Johnson's correspondence is also with numerous artist friends and others, including John F. and Margaret Carlson, Florence Ballin Cramer, Jo Davidson, Florence Lucius, Walter Frankl, Lila Wheelock Howard, Henry Lee McFee, Mary Riley, Lee Simonson, Lindsey Morris Sterling, Alice Morgan Wright, Mabel Dodge Luhan, and Vera Spier Kuhn. Letters to her son Alfred are quite detailed and revealing. Writings are by Dasburg, Johnson, and others. Johnson's writings include a very brief diary and her poetry. Writings by others are about the Taos and New Mexico art communities. Printed materials about both artists include clippings and exhibition catalogs. There are numerous photographs of Dasburg and Johnson, individually and together, and with friends and family. Of note are a group photograph of Birge Harrison's art class in Woodstock, New York, which includes Johnson and Dasburg, and a photograph of Dasburg with friends Konrad Cramer and John Reed. Dasburg's papers also include snapshots of Florence Lucius, Konrad and Florence Ballin Cramer, Frieda and D. H. Lawrence, and Mabel Dodge Luhan. Original artwork by the two artists include two sketchbooks by Johnson and three prints and two drawings by Dasburg.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following terms:
Subjects:
Kuhn, Vera, d. 1961; Cramer, Florence Ballin, 1884-1962; Lockwood, Ward; McFee, Henry Lee, 1886-1953; Hartley, Marsden, 1877-1943; Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1879-1962; Carlson, John F., 1874-1945; Wright, Alice Morgan, 1881-1975; Sterling, Lindsey, 1876-1931; Simonson, Lee, 1888-; Riley, Mary G., 1883-1939; Howard, Lila; Davidson, Florence Lucius, d. 1962; Davidson, Jo, 1883-1952; Frankl, Walter
Subjects-Topical:
Painters -- New York (State); Painters -- New Mexico; Sculptors -- New York (State); Artist colonies -- New York (State); Artist colonies -- New Mexico
Types of Materials:
Works of art; Poetry; Diaries; Sketchbooks; Photographs
Names:
Johnson, Grace Mott, 1882-1967
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 2 series of each artist's papers:
Series 1: Andrew Dasburg Papers, circa 1900-1980 (Box 1-7; 6.0 linear feet)
Series 2: Grace Mott Johnson Papers, 1833-1963 (Box 7-10; 2.8 linear feet)
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- Andrew Dasburg Papers, circa 1900-1980, Series 1:; (Box 1-6; 6.0 linear feet)
  This series contains the papers Andrew Dasburg, documenting both his personal life, such as his relationship with first wife, Grace Mott Johnson, and his friendships with many artists in New Mexico and New York, and to a lesser degree, his professional activities as an exhibiting artist. Found here are scattered legal, biographical, and financial documents. There is extensive correspondence with Johnson. Additional correspondence is with his son Alfred Dasburg, second wife Nancy Lane, and third wife Marina Wister, as well as numerous friends, fellow artists, scholars, galleries, universities, and museums. Notable correspondents include Mabel Dodge Luhan, Kenneth Adams, Thomas Hart Benton, George Biddle, Marsden Hartley, Ward Lockwood, Alfred Stieglitz, and Ward Lockwood, Henry Lee McFee, among many others.
  Also found in Dasburg's papers are a few essays on art written by him, and writings by others about Dasburg and more general art topics. Printed material consists of published books about the Taos art community, as well as exhibition announcements, catalogs, and newsclippings about Dasburg, other artists, and the Taos and New Mexico art community. Photographs are of Dasburg while he was living in Woodstock, New York; Paris, France; and Taos, New Mexico; as well as his family, friends, models, places, and works of art. Of note are a group photograph of Birge Harrison's art class in Woodstock, New York, which includes Johnson and Dasburg, and a photograph of Dasburg with friends Konrad Cramer and John Reed. Dasburg's artwork includes three prints and two drawings.
  Scattered papers of his son, Alfred Dasburg, primarily consists of correspondence with family, friends, and concerning the business affairs of his father.
  The Andrew Dasburg Papers are arranged into 7 subseries:
  1.1: Biographical Material & Business Records, 1913-1980
  1.2: Correspondence, circa 1906-1979
  1.3: Writings, circa 1940s-1979
  1.4: Printed Material, 1922-1980
  1.5: Photographs, circa 1900-1978
  1.6: Artwork, undated
  1.7: Alfred Dasburg Papers, 1914-1980
  The bulk of this series has been scanned in its entirety. Material not scanned includes duplicates, photographs of artwork and animals, slides, books, cancelled checks, miscellaneous financial and estate materials of limited research value, blank postcards and selected printed materials.
  - Biographical Material & Business Records, 1913-1980, 1.1:
    Found here are scattered biographical documents about Andrew Dasburg as well as business and legal records. Included are two biographical chronologies, one specifically documenting his time in London and Paris in 1914. Also found are the divorce agreements between Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson, and other legal documents, including a handwritten draft of his will from 1922. Other material includes awards and membership certificates, his death certificate, and the records of his estate, which was managed by his son Alfred, and includes inventories of his artwork at the time of his death, as well as other financial forms and notes.
    Business records primarily document Dasburg's late career during the 1970s. Included are the contracts and records of his work on a series of lithographs which were printed with the support of the Tamarind Institute, and the exhibition records for the Santa Fe Armory show which featured his work. This file also includes notes on Dasburg's participation in the 1913 Armory Show in New York. Other documents include an inventory of books in his home at the time of his death, a desk diary primarily containing addresses, and various lists of his artwork, some of which also include prices. A small amount of financial material consists of receipts for sale of his artwork, a ledger, cancelled checks and other miscellaneous items such as bank statements and insurance and tax forms. Items are arranged chronologically within each folder.
    - Biographical Chronologies, circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dasburg-Johnson Divorce Agreements, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Awards & Membership Certificates, 1913-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Tamarind Institute Contracts & Printing Records, 1970, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Santa Fe Armory Show Records, 1977-1978, (Partially scanned) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Certificate of Death, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Estate Records, 1979-1980, (Partially scanned) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Inventory of Books in Dasburg Home, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Desk Diary, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Lists of Artwork, 1947, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Legal Documents, 1922, 1941-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Financial Material (Box 1)
      - Sales of Artwork, 1928, 1957, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Ledger, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Cancelled Checks, 1935-1937, 1954-1955, (Not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1924, 1936-1979, (Not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, circa 1906-1979, 1.2:
    Found here is Andrew Dasburg's extensive correspondence which spans over seventy years, documenting both his personal and professional life. One third of the correspondence is between Dasburg and his first wife, Grace Mott Johnson. most of which was written during their marriage. These candid letters discuss daily activities, social events, travels, including Dasburg's time in Paris in 1910 and trip to Europe in 1914, news of mutual friends, artwork, and problems with their relationship.
    Also found is Dasburg's correspondence with his second wife, Nancy Lane around the time of their marriage in 1928, and correspondence with his third wife, Marina Wister Dasburg during the periods that she visited her family in Pennsylvania; most of these letters are written by Marina. Dasburg's correspondence with his son, Alfred, consists of brief letters sharing news of their travels, family, and personal matters.
    General correspondence primarily consists of Dasburg's correspondence with other family members, friends, colleagues, scholars, universities, and galleries. Where they exist, Dasburg's outgoing letters are interfiled with letters he received in a chronological arrangement. Dasburg was friends with many artists who, like him, were part of regional art colonies in Taos and Santa Fe, New Mexico, and Woodstock, New York. He also maintained friendships with artists he met in Europe and other travels and at the Art Students' League. Correspondents includes Kenneth Adams, Thomas Hart Benton, George Biddle, Dorothy Brett, Alexander Brook, Lucienne Chinard Clemens, Howard Cook, Russell Cowles, Vida Hunt Francis, Lewis Garrison, Marsden Hartley, Norbert Heerman, Richard Hollander, Lila Wheelock Howard, Charles Kassler, Mary Aubrey Keating, Carl Eric Lindin, Ward Lockwood, Erle Loran, Hayes Lyon, Henry Lee McFee, John Gaw Meem, Loren Mozley, Dickson Reeder, Louis Ribak, Paul Rohland, Alfred Stieglitz, Earl Stroh, Carl Van Vechten, Alice Morgan Wright, and Stanton Macdonald-Wright, among many others. Dasburg also corresponded with many former students including Edwin Gamble, Willard Nash, Alice Naylor, and Earl Stroh. Also found are letters from writers John Howard Griffin, Witter Bynner and Miriam Hapgood De Witt as well as art critics and historians such as Robert M. Coates, Oliver Larkin, and Stanley Lothrop. Dasburg maintained extensive correspondence with close friend, art patron and Taos resident, Mabel Dodge Luhan.
    A small amount of correspondence with galleries, universities, museums, curators, and scholars concerns exhibitions, sales, or research. Additional topics found within his correspondence are American Indian rights in New Mexico and his medical treatment for Addison's disease.
    See Index A for a select list of correspondents.
    Index A: Correspondents from Series 1.2: Andrew Dasburg Papers, General Correspondence
    Acker, Alice: 1972
    Adams, Kenneth M.: 1934, 1937, 1942, 1944, 1945, 1949, 1953, 1958
    Adolph and Esther Gottlieb Foundation, Inc.: 1979
    Aiello, Stan: 1973
    Albuquerque Art Gallery: 1948
    Allen, Arthur: 1948
    Allen, Robert F.: 1974
    American Artist: 1977, 1979
    Apodaca, Jerry & Clara: 1976-1978
    American Federation of Arts: 1946
    Artists of the Rockies: 1975, 1976
    Atkinson, Carla: 1929, 1933, 1934, 1936, 1938, 1940, 1941
    Bakos, Teresa: 1936
    Barker, William J.: 1935
    Barnouw, A. J.: 1942
    Beaudette, Barbara: 1973, 1974
    Bell, Larry: 1978
    Benjamin, Stanton: 1973
    Bennett, Wells: 1953
    Benton, Thomas Hart: 1937, 1939
    Biddle, George & Constance: 1934-1936, 1938
    Blumenschein, Ernest L.: 1951
    Bonham, Valeria Langeloth: 1949
    Bradenburgh, Beulah A.: 1944
    Bradenburgh, Margaret Caspar: 1910, 1941-1949, 1951
    Bradenburgh, Mathilda: 1940
    Bradley, John H. (Jack): 1934, 1935, 1955
    Breithut, Florence: 1952, 1953
    Brett, Dorothy: 1934, 1953
    Brinig, Myron: 1943
    Brook, Alex: 1971, 1972, 1974
    Browning, Hattie Louise: 1972
    Burkhard, Paul: 1954
    Bynner, Witter (Hal): 1934, 1939
    Bywaters, Jerry: 1948
    Carlin, E. J.: 1940
    Carnegie Institute: 1928
    Caspar, Angela: 1917
    Catron, Fletcher A.: 1947
    Chapellier Gallery: 1963
    Clark, Henry P.: 1952
    Clemens, Lucienne Chinard: 1941-1943, 1945, 1946, 1973, 1977
    Coates, Robert M.: 1950
    Cook, Howard: 1939, 1950, 1971-1978
    Comeau, Martin F.: 1946
    Cowles, Russell: 1934
    Cramer, Florence Ballin: 1945
    Creese, Walter L.: 1949
    Crown, Keith: 1973
    Cutting, Bronson: 1934
    Dasburg, Mrs. Donald: 1962
    Dasburg, Margaret (Mother): 1909, 1928-1930, 1934-1939, 1942-1948
    Dasburg, Matilda: 1942, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1952
    Davenport, Florence: 1941
    Davis, Herbert: 1935
    Dedrick, Philip: 1953
    De Loache, Ben: 1936, 1951
    de Schulthess, Mimi: 1954, 1955, 1958
    De Witt, Miriam Hapgood: 1972
    Diamond, Martin: 1972, 1973
    Dietrich, Margretta S.: 1947
    Dorman, Teresa & Jo: 1928
    Douglass, Ralph: 1953
    Dozier, Otis: 1952
    Dunne, Brian Boru: 1933
    Eastman, Dan: 1928
    Eckert, Josephine (Jo): 1941-1943, 1950
    Ellis, Bob: 1971
    Ellis, Erendira: 1976
    Erickson, R. J.: 1953
    Erwin, Dorothy Sanford: 1972, 1973, 1977
    Etting, Emlen: 1936
    Everingham, Mill: 1945
    Fergusson, Erna: 1949
    Ferren, John: 1931
    First National Bank: 1954, 1958
    Fisher, Alan: 1953, 1974
    Francis, Vida Hunt: 1952, 1953, 1955
    Gamble, Ed: 1950-1954, 1959, 1972, 1976, 1977
    Gardner, Virginia: 1972-1978
    Garrison, Lewis: 1948-1951, 1953
    Goodwin, Mary: 1972
    Graham, Donald S.: 1971-1976, 1978
    Griffin, Mrs. H. S.: 1952-1954
    Griffin, John H. (Howard): 1954
    Guthrie-Smith, Emily: 1975
    Hagerman, H.: 1929, 1933
    Hall, Robert M.: 1944, 1945
    Hamlin, Mary: 1953
    Harper, Pauline: 1950, 1953
    Harper, Larry: 1948, 1953
    Hartley, Marsden: 1932
    Hausner, Eric P.: 1951
    Hayes, Marian: 1954
    Heerman, Norbert: 1945, 1946
    Hollander, Richard (Dick) & Gertrude: 1942, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1952, 1953, 1972-1974, 1976, 1977
    Howard, Lila Wheelock: 1910, 1911, 1914, 1932, 1939-1943, 1951, 1957-1967
    Humphrey, Robert: 1972
    Hurt, Bessie: 1975, 1977
    Jackson, Jack T.: 1972
    Johnson, Frances H.: 1919
    Johnson, Helena McClure: 1954
    Johnson, Van Cleve: 1914
    Jones, Hester: 1949
    Kassler, Charles: 1932, 1935, 1936, 1978
    Kearns, John J.: 1928
    Keating, Mary Aubrey: 1941, 1944, 1945, 1949
    Kerr, Katherine: 1967
    Keyes, Walter A.: 1919
    King, Clinton: 1934
    Kostka, Bob: 1973, 1977
    La Farge, Oliver (Gallup Inter-tribal Indian Ceremonial): 1933
    Landreth, John: 1974
    Larkin, Oliver W.: 1948
    Lee, Freddie Dohle: 1914
    Lerenby, Frieda: 1973-1976
    Light, Gertrude: 1940, 1941
    Lindin, Carl Eric: 1937
    Linn, Ruth S.: 1973
    Lockwood, Ward: 1934, 1937, 1946, 1950, 1952-1954
    Loran, Erle: 1938, 1973, 1977
    Lothrop, Stanley: 1942
    Luhan, Mabel Dodge: 1924, 1928, 1935, 1937-1939, 1947, 1950-1952
    Lyon, Hayes: 1936, 1938-1948, 1950, 1953, 1973-1978
    M. O'Brien & Son: 1912
    Macdonald-Wright, Stanton: 1944
    Maclown, Eugene: 1934
    Macomb, Edith H.: 1937, 1938, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1949
    Mangravite, Peppino: 1938, 1939
    McCarty, Jacqueline Quinn: 1972, 1977
    McFee, Henry Lee: 1913, 1937-1943, 1945, 1949, 1950, 1952
    McKinney, Roland: 1944
    Mechau, Frank: 1937, 1943
    Meem, John Gaw: 1934, 1953
    Merrick, Vaughn: 1946
    Miller, Francis: 1947
    Modrall, Constance C.: 1974
    Mondragon, Joe E. & Lucila: 1937-1940
    Montenegro, Enrique: 1948
    Montgomery, Arthur: 1950-1952
    Morton-Morris, Mattie Sevier: 1949
    Mozley, Loren: 1971, 1974, 1976
    Museum of New Mexico: 19491976
    Nabut, Frances: 1943
    Nadejena, Lydia: 1952
    Nash, Willard: 1933, 1935
    Naylor, Alice: 1941
    Nebraska Art Association: 1976
    New Mexico Association of Indian Affairs: 1947
    Newton, George N.: 1977
    Norman, Dorothy: 1949
    Oakland Art Gallery: 1943, 1945, 1948
    Park, Deborah: 1971, 1973, 1977-1979
    Peters, Fritz: 1953
    Pijoan, Michel: 1954
    Pollock, Duncan: 1974
    Posey, Samuel Felton: 1935
    Post, Alan: 1952
    Putnam, Phelps: 1935
    Pyle, William Scott: 1935, 1937
    Rayburn, Dorothy: 1976
    Reed, Henry M.: 1972
    Reeder, Dickson: 1954
    Ribak, Louis: 1953, 1954
    Rodakiewicz, Henwar: 1936
    Rogoway, Marjorie: 1954, 1973
    Rohland, Paul & Caroline: 1915, 1949
    Ronnebeck, Arnold: 1934
    Roswell Museum and Art Center: 1974
    Rowntree, Leonard G.: 1938, 1940-1942, 1945, 1950, 1952-1954
    Santa Fe Festival of the Arts: 1978-1979
    Saunders, Sallie: 1953
    Saylor, Jeannette: 1978
    Schriever, George (The Anschutz Collection): 1973-1976
    Schwalbe, Diana: 1967, 1971, 1975, 1977
    Seres, Monique: 1970, 1973
    Shearer, Ivy: 1950, 1952, 1953
    Shearer, Augustus Hunt (Chuck) & Sally: 1957
    Simonson, Lee: 1914
    Simonson, Omar: 1914
    Slusser, Jean Paul: 1947, 1948
    Smith, Judson: 1952, 1953, 1956
    Solomon, Hyde: 1972
    Sternberg, Edward: 1943
    Stieglitz, Alfred: 1931
    Stokes, Mrs. Walter (Fanny): 1939-1944
    Stroh, Earl: 1948-1950, 1952, 1954
    Stuart, John: 1935